<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Comms Channel on TheCommsChannel</title>
    <link>https://www.thecommschannel.com/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Comms Channel on TheCommsChannel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 21:02:02 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.thecommschannel.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SIGINT</title>
      <link>https://www.thecommschannel.com/sigint/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 21:02:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.thecommschannel.com/sigint/index.html</guid>
      <description>SIGINT for Civilians Empowering Civilians through Signals Intelligence
Signals Intelligence (SIGINT) is generally attributed to government activities, but our website and YouTube focuses on how the civilians can use SIGINT tools and techniques for enhancing safety or even to complement your radio or aviation hobbies. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an individual concerned about personal security, a community-minded person looking to enhance your preparedness, or even augment your aviation photography/monitoring hobby, our website and YouTube channel are here to equip you with the knowledge and skills to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRa</title>
      <link>https://www.thecommschannel.com/lora/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.thecommschannel.com/lora/index.html</guid>
      <description>Discover LoRa: Revolutionizing Wireless Connectivity Unlock the Potential of Long-Range, Low-Power Communication
What is LoRa Technology?
LoRa (Long-Range) is a cutting-edge wireless communication technology designed for low-power, long-distance connectivity. It enables devices to transmit data over extended ranges while conserving battery life, making it ideal for off-grid and emergency communications.
Why Use LoRa Technology?
Extended Range: LoRa technology can cover vast distances, allowing you to connect devices in remote areas, across cities, and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio 101</title>
      <link>https://www.thecommschannel.com/radio101/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.thecommschannel.com/radio101/index.html</guid>
      <description>Radio 101 These pages are for a series dedicated to the basics of radio, but from a broader perspective outside of just ham radio. We&amp;rsquo;ve noticed a common theme online where people are wanting to learn more about radio, but much of the info is very ham radio focused. While ham radio is great, it’s not the only option and there may be a better option for your needs, so we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to create a series that delves into a broader spectrum of radio options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ham Radio</title>
      <link>https://www.thecommschannel.com/hamradio/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.thecommschannel.com/hamradio/index.html</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the World of Ham Radio Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned operator or a complete beginner, our website and YouTube videos provide in-depth tutorials and information into the world of amateur radio.
What is Ham Radio?
Ham radio, also known as amateur radio, is a unique hobby that allows individuals to explore many aspects of wireless communication. Unlike traditional radio services, ham radio operators have the freedom to experiment with a large number of frequencies in the ham bands, modes, and equipment.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>